http://circlecityflyers.com/index.php/resources/2015-09-17-15-44-41/privacy-policy

HomePrivate MessagingClassifiedsAdsClub StuffFAQsField InfoBylawsNewsletter20192020Latest NewslettersTerms and Conditions
MembershipPDF ApplicationOnline application Club filesFun Fly sign up formResources
EventsEvent calendarSearch eventsFeatured ArticlesOur supportersWebsitePrivacy PolicySite TermsTutorials
Photos & VideosView GalleryVideosContact UsOur BoardWebmaster
Privacy Policy
Log in
Register
Login to your account
Don't have an account yet?
Register now!
Username *
Password *
Remember Me
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Create an account
Fields marked with an asterisk (*) are required.
Register
HomePrivate MessagingClassifiedsAdsClub StuffFAQsField InfoBylawsNewsletter20192020Latest NewslettersTerms and ConditionsMembershipPDF ApplicationOnline application Club filesFun Fly sign up formResourcesEventsEvent calendarSearch eventsFeatured ArticlesOur supportersWebsitePrivacy PolicySite TermsTutorialsPhotos & VideosView GalleryVideosContact UsOur BoardWebmaster
Privacy Policy
Print
Details
Written by Super User
Category: Club stuff
Published: 16 September 2015
Hits: 13803
Commitment to Privacy
Circle City Flyers, Inc. understands the importance ofprotecting the privacy of Circlecityflyers.com users. The information collectedon the Circlecityflyers.com website is used to market and improve the serviceswe and our subsidiaries offer, to improve the Circlecityflyers.com web sitecontent, and to contact you with updates to the web site or for other marketingpurposes. Certain areas of Circlecityflyers.com, including thoseareas used to make purchases, require registration and/or a password foraccess. Information obtained from registered users of these areas may also beused for Circlecityflyers.com marketing purposes, and cookies may be used inthose and other areas, as is described in this Policy. Information obtained inthese areas may also be used in accordance with agreements governing access toand use of the specific areas. In addition, visitors to Circlecityflyers.comwill need to register for a Circlecityflyers.com Login user ID and password touse many of the interactive features on Circlecityflyers.com as well as to makea purchase or file an order from Circlecityflyers.com. Log file data and otherinformation gathered from registered users of Circlecityflyers.com are used toimprove the Circlecityflyers.com customer experience.
The Circlecityflyers.com web server uses an extendedlog file format which captures: date and time of visit, referring address(location from which a visitor comes to Circlecityflyers.com), type of Internetbrowser, and visitor's IP address. (Each computer that connects to the Internetis assigned a unique number, an IP address, for identification purposes). Thelog file does not capture a visitor's email address.
Cookies
A cookie is a series of data characters that, whenprogrammed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser'sapplication folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookiewill allow the web site to "recognize" you as a unique individual. Circlecityflyers.comuses these Cookies to personalize information for certain segments of itscustomer base. Secondly, in some instances, cookies are used to allow Circlecityflyers.comthe opportunity to associate individual customers with their informationprofiles. For example, through the use of cookies, Circlecityflyers.com can"remember" your user ID when you login to Circlecityflyers.com onyour computer. Should you choose to do so, cookies can be removed from yourhard drive and certain web browsers can be set so that cookies are not used orsaved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removingcookies.
Security
For the safety of our customers who are shoppingonline, Circlecityflyers.com always has security measures in place to protectcustomer information. Circlecityflyers.com takes all reasonable precautions toprotect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of your personalinformation under our control. Because the security of your personalinformation is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that itis processed confidentially, accurately and securely. The Circlecityflyers.compurchases use encryption technology, such as Secure Socket Layer (SSL)technology, which is supported by the vast majority of modern Internetbrowsers. SSL technology represents the highest level of security available onthe Internet, automatically encrypting information traveling over the Internet,verifying the identity of the transacting servers through certificates anddigital signatures, and confirming that the integrity of the message content ismaintained throughout its transmission. Circlecityflyers.com cannot ensure orwarrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and youdo so at your own risk.
Contact Circlecityflyers.com?
Our postal address is:
Circle City Flyers Inc.
PO Box 6307
Corona, California
92878
We can be reached via our contact page. CircleCity Flyers, Inc. reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any timewith or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes.
Your use of Circlecityflyers.com constitutes youragreement to this Privacy Policy.
Prev
Next
Copyright © 2020.
Circle City Flyers.
Fields marked with an asterisk (*) are required.
Register
Desktop Version
